Nathalia Andrea Flórez González

BILINGUAL RECRUITER

+57 3184062715

nathalia.florez@solvoglobal.com

Bucaramanga, Colombia

Bilingual psychologist and recruiter, with experiencie in cognitive behaivioral intervention and knowledge and experience in the organizational areal, management of profiles and interview. Responsible person, quick learner, organized, dedicated, hard-working person and capable to work independently. Creative mind and always up for new challenges and experiences, honest, team worker, organized and oriented to helping others.

EDUCATION

Psychologist degree 2014-2019

Universidad Autónoma de Bucaramanga

High School Graduate 2013

Sagrado corazón de Jesús hermanas Bethlemitas School

EXPERIENCE

Bilingual Recruiter
July 2022 - Currently

Solvo Global Multitasking and time management skills and abilities to manage social media and job platforms. Psychologist in recruitment dept Jan 2019 - July 2019

Jniversidad Autónima de Bucaramanga Support in the human resources process, assignment of psychotechnical interview, sent, application and qualification of psychotechnical tests. Psychologist intern July 2018 - Nov 2018

Clínica San Pablo S.A.
Individual attention to hospitalized patients with different pathologies, individual attention to rehab patients and development of psychoeducational workshops.

SKILLS

Languages

- English level B2
- Native Spanish

Soft skills

- Collaboration
- Time management
- Teamwork
- Organizational
- · Work ethic
- Active learning

Hard Skills

- Microsoft Office
- Human resourcess processes
- Recruitment platforms